List<Map<String, dynamic>> quiz = [
  {
    'level': 1,
    "questions": [
      {
        "question": "Who were famous for their work in the field of philosophy: Socrates, Plato, and Aristotle?",
        "options": ["Physics", "Mathematics", "Philosophy", "Chemistry"],
        "correct_answer": "Philosophy"
      },
      {
        "question": "How often did the Greeks hold the Olympic Games?",
        "options": ["Every year", "Every two years", "Every four years", "Once every four years"],
        "correct_answer": "Once every four years"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which Greek god was feared for his wrath over Odysseus' perilous journey and eventually helped him return home after several years?",
        "options": ["Poseidon", "Zeus", "Hades", "Apollo"],
        "correct_answer": "Poseidon"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is the 'Acropolis' known as in Ancient Greece?",
        "options": ["Marketplace", "Fortress", "Library", "Observatory"],
        "correct_answer": "Fortress"
      },
      {
        "question": "What type of literature were the Greeks known for?",
        "options": ["Scientific texts", "Political treaties", "Literary works", "Basic knowledge"],
        "correct_answer": "Literary works"
      },
      {
        "question": "What element is Artemis associated with?",
        "options": ["Fire", "Water", "Earth", "Hunt"],
        "correct_answer": "Hunt"
      },
      {
        "question": "What crops are associated with Demeter?",
        "options": ["Fruits and vegetables", "Fire", "Cattle", "Grains"],
        "correct_answer": "Fruits and vegetables"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which musical instrument is often depicted with Dionysus?",
        "options": ["Keyboard", "Trumpet", "Lantern", "Historical marketplace"],
        "correct_answer": "Trumpet"
      },
      {
        "question": "What term did the Greeks use to refer to 'good news'?",
        "options": ["Helot", "Spartan", "Athenian", "Myrmidon"],
        "correct_answer": "Helot"
      },
      {
        "question": "What did the Greeks use frozen yogurt and honey for?",
        "options": ["Tea", "Water", "Food preservation", "Consumption"],
        "correct_answer": "Consumption"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    'level': 2,
    "questions": [
      {
        "question": "Which work did Homer write?",
        "options": ["The Odyssey", "The Iliad", "Antigone", "Oedipus Rex"],
        "correct_answer": "The Iliad"
      },
      {
        "question": "What communication methods existed in Ancient Greece?",
        "options": ["Telephone", "Email", "News service", "Runners"],
        "correct_answer": "Runners"
      },
      {
        "question": "Pythagoras is known for his work in which field?",
        "options": ["Sacred geometry", "Naturalism", "Medieval philosophy", "Geometry"],
        "correct_answer": "Geometry"
      },
      {
        "question": "For how long did Pericles lead Athens?",
        "options": ["10 years", "20 years", "30 years", "40 years"],
        "correct_answer": "30 years"
      },
      {
        "question": "What was the programming language of Ancient Greece?",
        "options": ["Greek", "Latin", "Greekish", "Code"],
        "correct_answer": "Greek"
      },
      {
        "question": "When did the Olympic Games begin?",
        "options": ["10 years ago", "100 years ago", "1000 years ago", "2000 years ago"],
        "correct_answer": "1000 years ago"
      },
      {
        "question": "What was an 'amphora' used for in Greek civilization?",
        "options": ["Storage", "Medicine", "Culture", "Water supply"],
        "correct_answer": "Storage"
      },
      {
        "question": "In Ancient Greece, what was the 'agora' used for?",
        "options": ["Commerce", "Medicine", "Culture", "Spirituality"],
        "correct_answer": "Commerce"
      },
      {
        "question": "What was a 'caryatid' in Ancient Greece?",
        "options": ["Architectural element", "Decorative pattern", "Earring", "Columns"],
        "correct_answer": "Architectural element"
      },
      {
        "question": "In which era did 'Hellenism' emerge?",
        "options": ["Previous era", "2nd century", "3rd century", "4th century"],
        "correct_answer": "2nd century"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    'level': 3,
    "questions": [
      {
        "question": "Who was the famous playwright known for 'Oedipus Rex'?",
        "options": ["Euripides", "Sophocles", "Aeschylus", "Herodotus"],
        "correct_answer": "Sophocles"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which Greek city-state was known for its military prowess?",
        "options": ["Sparta", "Athens", "Thebes", "Corinth"],
        "correct_answer": "Sparta"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the famous Greek physician known as the 'Father of Medicine'?",
        "options": ["Pythagoras", "Hippocrates", "Plato", "Aristotle"],
        "correct_answer": "Hippocrates"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which event led to the defeat of the Persian Empire by the Greeks?",
        "options": ["Battle of Thermopylae", "Battle of Marathon", "Battle of Salamis", "Battle of Troy"],
        "correct_answer": "Battle of Marathon"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the legendary king of Ithaca, known for his cunning and resourcefulness?",
        "options": ["Agamemnon", "Perseus", "Heracles", "Odysseus"],
        "correct_answer": "Odysseus"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which Greek philosopher is credited with the concept of the 'Golden Mean'?",
        "options": ["Socrates", "Plato", "Aristotle", "Pythagoras"],
        "correct_answer": "Aristotle"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the patron goddess of wisdom, craft, and warfare?",
        "options": ["Athena", "Hera", "Artemis", "Persephone"],
        "correct_answer": "Athena"
      },
      {
        "question": "What type of government did Ancient Athens have?",
        "options": ["Monarchy", "Oligarchy", "Democracy", "Dictatorship"],
        "correct_answer": "Democracy"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which Greek philosopher is known for the saying 'Know thyself'?",
        "options": ["Plato", "Aristotle", "Socrates", "Pythagoras"],
        "correct_answer": "Socrates"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which of the following is a Greek architectural order characterized by its simplicity?",
        "options": ["Doric", "Ionic", "Corinthian", "Tuscan"],
        "correct_answer": "Doric"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    'level': 4,
    "questions": [
      {
        "question": "Who was the famous Greek mathematician known for his theorem about right triangles?",
        "options": ["Euclid", "Pythagoras", "Archimedes", "Eudoxus"],
        "correct_answer": "Pythagoras"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which Greek goddess was the protector of marriage and family?",
        "options": ["Aphrodite", "Hera", "Artemis", "Demeter"],
        "correct_answer": "Hera"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the god of the underworld and the ruler of the dead?",
        "options": ["Zeus", "Hades", "Poseidon", "Apollo"],
        "correct_answer": "Hades"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which Greek hero was known for his incredible strength?",
        "options": ["Heracles", "Perseus", "Achilles", "Theseus"],
        "correct_answer": "Heracles"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which Greek playwright wrote 'The Persians'?",
        "options": ["Sophocles", "Euripides", "Aeschylus", "Aristophanes"],
        "correct_answer": "Aeschylus"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which battle marked the end of the Peloponnesian War?",
        "options": ["Battle of Thermopylae", "Battle of Salamis", "Battle of Plataea", "Battle of Amphipolis"],
        "correct_answer": "Battle of Amphipolis"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the patron god of music, poetry, and the sun?",
        "options": ["Apollo", "Dionysus", "Hephaestus", "Hermes"],
        "correct_answer": "Apollo"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which Greek goddess was born fully grown and armored from Zeus' forehead?",
        "options": ["Athena", "Artemis", "Persephone", "Hera"],
        "correct_answer": "Athena"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the goddess of love, beauty, and desire?",
        "options": ["Athena", "Artemis", "Aphrodite", "Hestia"],
        "correct_answer": "Aphrodite"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which ancient Greek historian is often referred to as the 'Father of History'?",
        "options": ["Herodotus", "Thucydides", "Xenophon", "Polybius"],
        "correct_answer": "Herodotus"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    'level': 5,
    "questions": [
      {
        "question": "Who was the founder of the Academy in Athens and the teacher of Aristotle?",
        "options": ["Plato", "Socrates", "Pythagoras", "Aristotle"],
        "correct_answer": "Plato"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which Greek city-state was known for its cultural and intellectual achievements?",
        "options": ["Athens", "Sparta", "Corinth", "Thebes"],
        "correct_answer": "Athens"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the famous Greek mathematician known for his work on geometry?",
        "options": ["Euclid", "Archimedes", "Eudoxus", "Pythagoras"],
        "correct_answer": "Euclid"
      },
      {
        "question": "What was the name of the famous Greek temple dedicated to Athena on the Acropolis of Athens?",
        "options": ["Parthenon", "Pantheon", "Acropolis", "Temple of Zeus"],
        "correct_answer": "Parthenon"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the Greek god of wine, fertility, and theater?",
        "options": ["Apollo", "Dionysus", "Hermes", "Hephaestus"],
        "correct_answer": "Dionysus"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which famous Greek philosopher was condemned to death by drinking hemlock?",
        "options": ["Aristotle", "Plato", "Pythagoras", "Socrates"],
        "correct_answer": "Socrates"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the goddess of hunting, wilderness, and childbirth?",
        "options": ["Artemis", "Athena", "Hera", "Demeter"],
        "correct_answer": "Artemis"
      },
      {
        "question": "What event marked the beginning of the Persian Wars?",
        "options": ["Battle of Thermopylae", "Battle of Marathon", "Battle of Salamis", "Battle of Plataea"],
        "correct_answer": "Battle of Marathon"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which Greek city-state was known for its militaristic society?",
        "options": ["Sparta", "Athens", "Thebes", "Corinth"],
        "correct_answer": "Sparta"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the patron god of blacksmiths, craftsmen, and volcanoes?",
        "options": ["Apollo", "Hephaestus", "Dionysus", "Hermes"],
        "correct_answer": "Hephaestus"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    'level': 6,
    "questions": [
      {
        "question": "Who was the famous Greek philosopher known for his dialogues and the Socratic method?",
        "options": ["Plato", "Aristotle", "Pythagoras", "Socrates"],
        "correct_answer": "Socrates"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which Greek playwright wrote the tragedies 'Medea' and 'The Trojan Women'?",
        "options": ["Sophocles", "Aeschylus", "Euripides", "Aristophanes"],
        "correct_answer": "Euripides"
      },
      {
        "question": "What was the name of the famous Greek physician known for his work on anatomy?",
        "options": ["Hippocrates", "Galen", "Herophilus", "Aristotle"],
        "correct_answer": "Herophilus"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which Greek mathematician calculated the value of pi and invented the screw pump?",
        "options": ["Euclid", "Archimedes", "Pythagoras", "Eudoxus"],
        "correct_answer": "Archimedes"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the hero of the 'Iliad', known for his invulnerability?",
        "options": ["Heracles", "Perseus", "Achilles", "Theseus"],
        "correct_answer": "Achilles"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which Greek philosopher founded the Academy in Athens?",
        "options": ["Socrates", "Plato", "Aristotle", "Pythagoras"],
        "correct_answer": "Plato"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the god of the sky and thunder?",
        "options": ["Poseidon", "Hades", "Zeus", "Apollo"],
        "correct_answer": "Zeus"
      },
      {
        "question": "What was the name of the famous temple dedicated to Apollo at Delphi?",
        "options": ["Parthenon", "Temple of Artemis", "Acropolis", "Temple of Apollo"],
        "correct_answer": "Temple of Apollo"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the Greek goddess of wisdom, craft, and warfare?",
        "options": ["Athena", "Hera", "Artemis", "Persephone"],
        "correct_answer": "Athena"
      },
      {
        "question": "What was the name of the sacred oracle of Apollo in Ancient Greece?",
        "options": ["Delphi", "Olympia", "Athens", "Sparta"],
        "correct_answer": "Delphi"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    'level': 7,
    "questions": [
      {
        "question": "Which Greek philosopher is known for his works 'The Republic' and 'The Symposium'?",
        "options": ["Socrates", "Aristotle", "Pythagoras", "Plato"],
        "correct_answer": "Plato"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the famous Greek mathematician known for his work on conic sections?",
        "options": ["Euclid", "Pythagoras", "Apollonius", "Eudoxus"],
        "correct_answer": "Apollonius"
      },
      {
        "question": "What was the name of the famous temple dedicated to Artemis in Ephesus?",
        "options": ["Parthenon", "Temple of Apollo", "Acropolis", "Temple of Artemis"],
        "correct_answer": "Temple of Artemis"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the goddess of the hearth, home, and family?",
        "options": ["Hestia", "Demeter", "Athena", "Aphrodite"],
        "correct_answer": "Hestia"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which Greek historian chronicled the history of the Peloponnesian War?",
        "options": ["Herodotus", "Thucydides", "Xenophon", "Polybius"],
        "correct_answer": "Thucydides"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the famous Greek philosopher known as the 'Father of Western Philosophy'?",
        "options": ["Socrates", "Aristotle", "Pythagoras", "Plato"],
        "correct_answer": "Socrates"
      },
      {
        "question": "What was the name of the famous Greek poet known for his epic poems 'The Iliad' and 'The Odyssey'?",
        "options": ["Homer", "Hesiod", "Aesop", "Pindar"],
        "correct_answer": "Homer"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which Greek city-state was known for its powerful navy?",
        "options": ["Athens", "Sparta", "Corinth", "Thebes"],
        "correct_answer": "Athens"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the famous Greek playwright known for his comedies such as 'Lysistrata' and 'The Clouds'?",
        "options": ["Sophocles", "Euripides", "Aeschylus", "Aristophanes"],
        "correct_answer": "Aristophanes"
      },
      {
        "question": "What was the name of the famous Greek temple dedicated to Zeus in Olympia?",
        "options": ["Parthenon", "Temple of Artemis", "Acropolis", "Temple of Zeus"],
        "correct_answer": "Temple of Zeus"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    'level': 8,
    "questions": [
      {
        "question": "Who was the famous Greek philosopher known as the 'Father of Metaphysics'?",
        "options": ["Socrates", "Aristotle", "Pythagoras", "Plato"],
        "correct_answer": "Aristotle"
      },
      {
        "question": "What was the name of the famous battle in which the Greeks defeated the Persians?",
        "options": ["Battle of Thermopylae", "Battle of Marathon", "Battle of Salamis", "Battle of Plataea"],
        "correct_answer": "Battle of Salamis"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the goddess of agriculture, fertility, and the harvest?",
        "options": ["Aphrodite", "Hera", "Artemis", "Demeter"],
        "correct_answer": "Demeter"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which Greek god was known as the god of the sea and earthquakes?",
        "options": ["Zeus", "Poseidon", "Hades", "Apollo"],
        "correct_answer": "Poseidon"
      },
      {
        "question": "What was the name of the famous school of philosophy founded by Plato?",
        "options": ["Epicureanism", "Stoicism", "Cynicism", "Academy"],
        "correct_answer": "Academy"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the famous Greek sculptor known for his statue of 'Athena Parthenos'?",
        "options": ["Phidias", "Praxiteles", "Polykleitos", "Lysippos"],
        "correct_answer": "Phidias"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which Greek goddess was known as the protector of women and marriage?",
        "options": ["Athena", "Hera", "Artemis", "Demeter"],
        "correct_answer": "Hera"
      },
      {
        "question": "What was the name of the famous Greek battle in which the outnumbered Spartans held off the Persian army?",
        "options": ["Battle of Thermopylae", "Battle of Marathon", "Battle of Salamis", "Battle of Plataea"],
        "correct_answer": "Battle of Thermopylae"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the Greek god of fire, metalworking, and craftsmanship?",
        "options": ["Apollo", "Dionysus", "Hephaestus", "Hermes"],
        "correct_answer": "Hephaestus"
      },
      {
        "question": "What was the name of the famous Greek mathematician known for his work on geometry?",
        "options": ["Euclid", "Archimedes", "Eudoxus", "Pythagoras"],
        "correct_answer": "Euclid"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    'level': 9,
    "questions": [
      {
        "question": "Who was the famous Greek philosopher known for his concept of atomism?",
        "options": ["Socrates", "Aristotle", "Pythagoras", "Democritus"],
        "correct_answer": "Democritus"
      },
      {
        "question": "What was the name of the famous Greek physician known for his work on anatomy?",
        "options": ["Hippocrates", "Galen", "Herophilus", "Aristotle"],
        "correct_answer": "Herophilus"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the god of wine, fertility, and theater?",
        "options": ["Apollo", "Dionysus", "Hermes", "Hephaestus"],
        "correct_answer": "Dionysus"
      },
      {
        "question": "What was the name of the famous temple dedicated to Athena on the Acropolis of Athens?",
        "options": ["Parthenon", "Pantheon", "Acropolis", "Temple of Zeus"],
        "correct_answer": "Parthenon"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the famous Greek mathematician known for his theorem about right triangles?",
        "options": ["Euclid", "Pythagoras", "Archimedes", "Eudoxus"],
        "correct_answer": "Pythagoras"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which Greek god was the protector of marriage and family?",
        "options": ["Aphrodite", "Hera", "Artemis", "Demeter"],
        "correct_answer": "Hera"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the god of the underworld and the ruler of the dead?",
        "options": ["Zeus", "Hades", "Poseidon", "Apollo"],
        "correct_answer": "Hades"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which Greek hero was known for his incredible strength?",
        "options": ["Heracles", "Perseus", "Achilles", "Theseus"],
        "correct_answer": "Heracles"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which Greek playwright wrote 'The Persians'?",
        "options": ["Sophocles", "Euripides", "Aeschylus", "Aristophanes"],
        "correct_answer": "Aeschylus"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which battle marked the end of the Peloponnesian War?",
        "options": ["Battle of Thermopylae", "Battle of Salamis", "Battle of Plataea", "Battle of Amphipolis"],
        "correct_answer": "Battle of Amphipolis"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    'level': 10,
    "questions": [
      {
        "question": "Who was the founder of the Academy in Athens and the teacher of Aristotle?",
        "options": ["Plato", "Socrates", "Pythagoras", "Aristotle"],
        "correct_answer": "Plato"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which Greek city-state was known for its cultural and intellectual achievements?",
        "options": ["Athens", "Sparta", "Corinth", "Thebes"],
        "correct_answer": "Athens"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the famous Greek mathematician known for his work on geometry?",
        "options": ["Euclid", "Archimedes", "Eudoxus", "Pythagoras"],
        "correct_answer": "Euclid"
      },
      {
        "question": "What was the name of the famous temple dedicated to Artemis in Ephesus?",
        "options": ["Parthenon", "Temple of Apollo", "Acropolis", "Temple of Artemis"],
        "correct_answer": "Temple of Artemis"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the goddess of the hearth, home, and family?",
        "options": ["Hestia", "Demeter", "Athena", "Aphrodite"],
        "correct_answer": "Hestia"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which Greek historian chronicled the history of the Peloponnesian War?",
        "options": ["Herodotus", "Thucydides", "Xenophon", "Polybius"],
        "correct_answer": "Thucydides"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the famous Greek philosopher known as the 'Father of Western Philosophy'?",
        "options": ["Socrates", "Aristotle", "Pythagoras", "Plato"],
        "correct_answer": "Socrates"
      },
      {
        "question": "What was the name of the famous Greek poet known for his epic poems 'The Iliad' and 'The Odyssey'?",
        "options": ["Homer", "Hesiod", "Aesop", "Pindar"],
        "correct_answer": "Homer"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which Greek city-state was known for its powerful navy?",
        "options": ["Athens", "Sparta", "Corinth", "Thebes"],
        "correct_answer": "Athens"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the famous Greek playwright known for his comedies such as 'Lysistrata' and 'The Clouds'?",
        "options": ["Sophocles", "Euripides", "Aeschylus", "Aristophanes"],
        "correct_answer": "Aristophanes"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    'level': 11,
    "questions": [
      {
        "question": "Who was the famous Greek philosopher known for his dialogues and the Socratic method?",
        "options": ["Plato", "Aristotle", "Pythagoras", "Socrates"],
        "correct_answer": "Socrates"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which Greek playwright wrote the tragedies 'Medea' and 'The Trojan Women'?",
        "options": ["Sophocles", "Aeschylus", "Euripides", "Aristophanes"],
        "correct_answer": "Euripides"
      },
      {
        "question": "What was the name of the famous Greek physician known for his work on anatomy?",
        "options": ["Hippocrates", "Galen", "Herophilus", "Aristotle"],
        "correct_answer": "Herophilus"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which Greek mathematician calculated the value of pi and invented the screw pump?",
        "options": ["Euclid", "Archimedes", "Pythagoras", "Eudoxus"],
        "correct_answer": "Archimedes"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the hero of the 'Iliad', known for his invulnerability?",
        "options": ["Heracles", "Perseus", "Achilles", "Theseus"],
        "correct_answer": "Achilles"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which Greek philosopher founded the Academy in Athens?",
        "options": ["Socrates", "Plato", "Aristotle", "Pythagoras"],
        "correct_answer": "Plato"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the god of the sky and thunder?",
        "options": ["Poseidon", "Hades", "Zeus", "Apollo"],
        "correct_answer": "Zeus"
      },
      {
        "question": "What was the name of the famous temple dedicated to Apollo at Delphi?",
        "options": ["Parthenon", "Temple of Artemis", "Acropolis", "Temple of Apollo"],
        "correct_answer": "Temple of Apollo"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the Greek goddess of wisdom, craft, and warfare?",
        "options": ["Athena", "Hera", "Artemis", "Persephone"],
        "correct_answer": "Athena"
      },
      {
        "question": "What was the name of the sacred oracle of Apollo in Ancient Greece?",
        "options": ["Delphi", "Olympia", "Athens", "Sparta"],
        "correct_answer": "Delphi"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    'level': 12,
    "questions": [
      {
        "question": "Who was the famous Greek philosopher known for his concept of atomism?",
        "options": ["Socrates", "Aristotle", "Pythagoras", "Democritus"],
        "correct_answer": "Democritus"
      },
      {
        "question": "What was the name of the famous Greek physician known for his work on anatomy?",
        "options": ["Hippocrates", "Galen", "Herophilus", "Aristotle"],
        "correct_answer": "Herophilus"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the god of wine, fertility, and theater?",
        "options": ["Apollo", "Dionysus", "Hermes", "Hephaestus"],
        "correct_answer": "Dionysus"
      },
      {
        "question": "What was the name of the famous temple dedicated to Athena on the Acropolis of Athens?",
        "options": ["Parthenon", "Pantheon", "Acropolis", "Temple of Zeus"],
        "correct_answer": "Parthenon"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the goddess of the hearth, home, and family?",
        "options": ["Hestia", "Demeter", "Athena", "Aphrodite"],
        "correct_answer": "Hestia"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which Greek historian chronicled the history of the Peloponnesian War?",
        "options": ["Herodotus", "Thucydides", "Xenophon", "Polybius"],
        "correct_answer": "Thucydides"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the famous Greek philosopher known as the 'Father of Western Philosophy'?",
        "options": ["Socrates", "Aristotle", "Pythagoras", "Plato"],
        "correct_answer": "Socrates"
      },
      {
        "question": "What was the name of the famous Greek poet known for his epic poems 'The Iliad' and 'The Odyssey'?",
        "options": ["Homer", "Hesiod", "Aesop", "Pindar"],
        "correct_answer": "Homer"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which Greek city-state was known for its powerful navy?",
        "options": ["Athens", "Sparta", "Corinth", "Thebes"],
        "correct_answer": "Athens"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the famous Greek playwright known for his comedies such as 'Lysistrata' and 'The Clouds'?",
        "options": ["Sophocles", "Euripides", "Aeschylus", "Aristophanes"],
        "correct_answer": "Aristophanes"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    'level': 13,
    "questions": [
      {
        "question": "Who was the famous Greek philosopher known for his work on ethics and virtue?",
        "options": ["Socrates", "Aristotle", "Plato", "Pythagoras"],
        "correct_answer": "Aristotle"
      },
      {
        "question": "What was the name of the famous temple dedicated to Hera in Olympia?",
        "options": ["Parthenon", "Temple of Artemis", "Acropolis", "Temple of Hera"],
        "correct_answer": "Temple of Hera"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the goddess of love, beauty, and desire?",
        "options": ["Hestia", "Athena", "Hera", "Aphrodite"],
        "correct_answer": "Aphrodite"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which Greek hero was known for his slaying of the Gorgon Medusa?",
        "options": ["Heracles", "Perseus", "Achilles", "Theseus"],
        "correct_answer": "Perseus"
      },
      {
        "question": "What was the name of the famous school of philosophy founded by Aristotle?",
        "options": ["Epicureanism", "Stoicism", "Cynicism", "Lyceum"],
        "correct_answer": "Lyceum"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the famous Greek playwright known for his tragedies such as 'Oedipus Rex'?",
        "options": ["Sophocles", "Euripides", "Aeschylus", "Aristophanes"],
        "correct_answer": "Sophocles"
      },
      {
        "question": "What was the name of the famous battle in which the Greeks defeated the Persians?",
        "options": ["Battle of Thermopylae", "Battle of Marathon", "Battle of Salamis", "Battle of Plataea"],
        "correct_answer": "Battle of Marathon"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the god of the underworld and the ruler of the dead?",
        "options": ["Zeus", "Hades", "Poseidon", "Apollo"],
        "correct_answer": "Hades"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which Greek mathematician calculated the value of pi and invented the screw pump?",
        "options": ["Euclid", "Archimedes", "Pythagoras", "Eudoxus"],
        "correct_answer": "Archimedes"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the goddess of agriculture, fertility, and the harvest?",
        "options": ["Aphrodite", "Hera", "Artemis", "Demeter"],
        "correct_answer": "Demeter"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    'level': 14,
    "questions": [
      {
        "question": "Who was the famous Greek historian known for his detailed account of the Peloponnesian War?",
        "options": ["Herodotus", "Thucydides", "Xenophon", "Polybius"],
        "correct_answer": "Thucydides"
      },
      {
        "question": "What was the name of the famous temple dedicated to Athena in Athens?",
        "options": ["Parthenon", "Pantheon", "Acropolis", "Temple of Zeus"],
        "correct_answer": "Parthenon"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the god of the sea and earthquakes?",
        "options": ["Zeus", "Poseidon", "Hades", "Apollo"],
        "correct_answer": "Poseidon"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which Greek city-state was known for its military prowess and discipline?",
        "options": ["Athens", "Sparta", "Corinth", "Thebes"],
        "correct_answer": "Sparta"
      },
      {
        "question": "What was the name of the famous school of philosophy founded by Plato?",
        "options": ["Epicureanism", "Stoicism", "Cynicism", "Academy"],
        "correct_answer": "Academy"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the famous Greek sculptor known for his statue of 'Athena Parthenos'?",
        "options": ["Phidias", "Praxiteles", "Polykleitos", "Lysippos"],
        "correct_answer": "Phidias"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which Greek goddess was known as the protector of women and marriage?",
        "options": ["Athena", "Hera", "Artemis", "Demeter"],
        "correct_answer": "Hera"
      },
      {
        "question": "What was the name of the famous Greek battle in which the outnumbered Spartans held off the Persian army?",
        "options": ["Battle of Thermopylae", "Battle of Marathon", "Battle of Salamis", "Battle of Plataea"],
        "correct_answer": "Battle of Thermopylae"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the Greek god of fire, metalworking, and craftsmanship?",
        "options": ["Apollo", "Dionysus", "Hephaestus", "Hermes"],
        "correct_answer": "Hephaestus"
      },
      {
        "question": "What was the name of the famous Greek mathematician known for his work on geometry?",
        "options": ["Euclid", "Archimedes", "Eudoxus", "Pythagoras"],
        "correct_answer": "Euclid"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    'level': 15,
    "questions": [
      {
        "question": "Who was the Greek goddess of wisdom, craft, and warfare?",
        "options": ["Athena", "Hera", "Artemis", "Persephone"],
        "correct_answer": "Athena"
      },
      {
        "question": "What was the name of the famous Greek battle in which the Athenians defeated the Persians?",
        "options": ["Battle of Thermopylae", "Battle of Marathon", "Battle of Salamis", "Battle of Plataea"],
        "correct_answer": "Battle of Marathon"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the Greek god of the sun, music, poetry, and prophecy?",
        "options": ["Zeus", "Apollo", "Hermes", "Dionysus"],
        "correct_answer": "Apollo"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which Greek philosopher was the student of Socrates and the teacher of Aristotle?",
        "options": ["Plato", "Aristotle", "Pythagoras", "Democritus"],
        "correct_answer": "Plato"
      },
      {
        "question": "What was the name of the famous temple dedicated to Hera in Olympia?",
        "options": ["Parthenon", "Temple of Artemis", "Acropolis", "Temple of Hera"],
        "correct_answer": "Temple of Hera"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the goddess of love, beauty, and desire?",
        "options": ["Hestia", "Athena", "Hera", "Aphrodite"],
        "correct_answer": "Aphrodite"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which Greek hero was known for his slaying of the Gorgon Medusa?",
        "options": ["Heracles", "Perseus", "Achilles", "Theseus"],
        "correct_answer": "Perseus"
      },
      {
        "question": "What was the name of the famous school of philosophy founded by Aristotle?",
        "options": ["Epicureanism", "Stoicism", "Cynicism", "Lyceum"],
        "correct_answer": "Lyceum"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the famous Greek playwright known for his tragedies such as 'Oedipus Rex'?",
        "options": ["Sophocles", "Euripides", "Aeschylus", "Aristophanes"],
        "correct_answer": "Sophocles"
      },
      {
        "question": "What was the name of the famous battle in which the Greeks defeated the Persians?",
        "options": ["Battle of Thermopylae", "Battle of Marathon", "Battle of Salamis", "Battle of Plataea"],
        "correct_answer": "Battle of Marathon"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    'level': 16,
    "questions": [
      {
        "question": "Who was the famous Greek historian known for his detailed account of the Peloponnesian War?",
        "options": ["Herodotus", "Thucydides", "Xenophon", "Polybius"],
        "correct_answer": "Thucydides"
      },
      {
        "question": "What was the name of the famous temple dedicated to Athena in Athens?",
        "options": ["Parthenon", "Pantheon", "Acropolis", "Temple of Zeus"],
        "correct_answer": "Parthenon"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the god of the sea and earthquakes?",
        "options": ["Zeus", "Poseidon", "Hades", "Apollo"],
        "correct_answer": "Poseidon"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which Greek city-state was known for its military prowess and discipline?",
        "options": ["Athens", "Sparta", "Corinth", "Thebes"],
        "correct_answer": "Sparta"
      },
      {
        "question": "What was the name of the famous school of philosophy founded by Plato?",
        "options": ["Epicureanism", "Stoicism", "Cynicism", "Academy"],
        "correct_answer": "Academy"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the famous Greek sculptor known for his statue of 'Athena Parthenos'?",
        "options": ["Phidias", "Praxiteles", "Polykleitos", "Lysippos"],
        "correct_answer": "Phidias"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which Greek goddess was known as the protector of women and marriage?",
        "options": ["Athena", "Hera", "Artemis", "Demeter"],
        "correct_answer": "Hera"
      },
      {
        "question": "What was the name of the famous Greek battle in which the outnumbered Spartans held off the Persian army?",
        "options": ["Battle of Thermopylae", "Battle of Marathon", "Battle of Salamis", "Battle of Plataea"],
        "correct_answer": "Battle of Thermopylae"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the Greek god of fire, metalworking, and craftsmanship?",
        "options": ["Apollo", "Dionysus", "Hephaestus", "Hermes"],
        "correct_answer": "Hephaestus"
      },
      {
        "question": "What was the name of the famous Greek mathematician known for his work on geometry?",
        "options": ["Euclid", "Archimedes", "Eudoxus", "Pythagoras"],
        "correct_answer": "Euclid"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    'level': 17,
    "questions": [
      {
        "question": "Who was the famous Greek philosopher known for his dialogues and the Socratic method?",
        "options": ["Plato", "Aristotle", "Pythagoras", "Socrates"],
        "correct_answer": "Socrates"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which Greek playwright wrote the tragedies 'Medea' and 'The Trojan Women'?",
        "options": ["Sophocles", "Aeschylus", "Euripides", "Aristophanes"],
        "correct_answer": "Euripides"
      },
      {
        "question": "What was the name of the famous Greek physician known for his work on anatomy?",
        "options": ["Hippocrates", "Galen", "Herophilus", "Aristotle"],
        "correct_answer": "Herophilus"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which Greek mathematician calculated the value of pi and invented the screw pump?",
        "options": ["Euclid", "Archimedes", "Pythagoras", "Eudoxus"],
        "correct_answer": "Archimedes"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the hero of the 'Iliad', known for his invulnerability?",
        "options": ["Heracles", "Perseus", "Achilles", "Theseus"],
        "correct_answer": "Achilles"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which Greek philosopher founded the Academy in Athens?",
        "options": ["Socrates", "Plato", "Aristotle", "Pythagoras"],
        "correct_answer": "Plato"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the god of the sky and thunder?",
        "options": ["Poseidon", "Hades", "Zeus", "Apollo"],
        "correct_answer": "Zeus"
      },
      {
        "question": "What was the name of the famous temple dedicated to Apollo at Delphi?",
        "options": ["Parthenon", "Temple of Artemis", "Acropolis", "Temple of Apollo"],
        "correct_answer": "Temple of Apollo"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the Greek goddess of wisdom, craft, and warfare?",
        "options": ["Athena", "Hera", "Artemis", "Persephone"],
        "correct_answer": "Athena"
      },
      {
        "question": "What was the name of the sacred oracle of Apollo in Ancient Greece?",
        "options": ["Delphi", "Olympia", "Athens", "Sparta"],
        "correct_answer": "Delphi"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    'level': 18,
    "questions": [
      {
        "question": "Who was the Greek philosopher known for his theory of forms and his allegory of the cave?",
        "options": ["Socrates", "Plato", "Aristotle", "Pythagoras"],
        "correct_answer": "Plato"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which Greek city-state was known for its democratic government and naval power?",
        "options": ["Athens", "Sparta", "Corinth", "Thebes"],
        "correct_answer": "Athens"
      },
      {
        "question": "What was the name of the famous temple dedicated to Artemis in Ephesus?",
        "options": ["Parthenon", "Temple of Artemis", "Acropolis", "Temple of Hera"],
        "correct_answer": "Temple of Artemis"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the goddess of the moon, hunting, and childbirth?",
        "options": ["Hestia", "Athena", "Artemis", "Aphrodite"],
        "correct_answer": "Artemis"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which Greek hero undertook the Twelve Labors as punishment for killing his family?",
        "options": ["Heracles", "Perseus", "Achilles", "Theseus"],
        "correct_answer": "Heracles"
      },
      {
        "question": "What was the name of the famous school of philosophy founded by Zeno of Citium?",
        "options": ["Epicureanism", "Stoicism", "Cynicism", "Academy"],
        "correct_answer": "Stoicism"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the famous Greek playwright known for his satirical comedies?",
        "options": ["Sophocles", "Euripides", "Aeschylus", "Aristophanes"],
        "correct_answer": "Aristophanes"
      },
      {
        "question": "What was the name of the famous battle in which the Greeks defeated the Persian fleet?",
        "options": ["Battle of Thermopylae", "Battle of Marathon", "Battle of Salamis", "Battle of Plataea"],
        "correct_answer": "Battle of Salamis"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the Greek god of wine, fertility, and theater?",
        "options": ["Apollo", "Dionysus", "Hermes", "Hephaestus"],
        "correct_answer": "Dionysus"
      },
      {
        "question": "What was the name of the famous Greek mathematician known for his work on number theory and geometry?",
        "options": ["Euclid", "Archimedes", "Eudoxus", "Pythagoras"],
        "correct_answer": "Pythagoras"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    'level': 19,
    "questions": [
      {
        "question": "Who was the famous Greek historian known as the 'Father of History'?",
        "options": ["Herodotus", "Thucydides", "Xenophon", "Polybius"],
        "correct_answer": "Herodotus"
      },
      {
        "question": "What was the name of the famous temple dedicated to Zeus in Olympia?",
        "options": ["Parthenon", "Temple of Artemis", "Acropolis", "Temple of Zeus"],
        "correct_answer": "Temple of Zeus"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the goddess of the hearth, home, and family?",
        "options": ["Hestia", "Demeter", "Athena", "Aphrodite"],
        "correct_answer": "Hestia"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which Greek hero was known for his journey to the underworld to rescue his wife, Eurydice?",
        "options": ["Orpheus", "Perseus", "Heracles", "Jason"],
        "correct_answer": "Orpheus"
      },
      {
        "question": "What was the name of the famous school of philosophy founded by Epicurus?",
        "options": ["Epicureanism", "Stoicism", "Cynicism", "Academy"],
        "correct_answer": "Epicureanism"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the famous Greek sculptor known for his statue of 'Aphrodite of Knidos'?",
        "options": ["Phidias", "Praxiteles", "Polykleitos", "Lysippos"],
        "correct_answer": "Praxiteles"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which Greek goddess was known as the virgin huntress?",
        "options": ["Athena", "Hera", "Artemis", "Demeter"],
        "correct_answer": "Artemis"
      },
      {
        "question": "What was the name of the famous battle in which the Greeks decisively defeated the Persians?",
        "options": ["Battle of Thermopylae", "Battle of Marathon", "Battle of Salamis", "Battle of Plataea"],
        "correct_answer": "Battle of Plataea"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the Greek god of messages, trade, and thieves?",
        "options": ["Zeus", "Hermes", "Poseidon", "Apollo"],
        "correct_answer": "Hermes"
      },
      {
        "question": "What was the name of the famous Greek mathematician known for his work on conic sections?",
        "options": ["Euclid", "Archimedes", "Eudoxus", "Apollonius"],
        "correct_answer": "Apollonius"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    'level': 20,
    "questions": [
      {
        "question": "Who was the famous Greek philosopher known for his concept of atomism?",
        "options": ["Socrates", "Aristotle", "Pythagoras", "Democritus"],
        "correct_answer": "Democritus"
      },
      {
        "question": "What was the name of the famous Greek physician known for his work on anatomy?",
        "options": ["Hippocrates", "Galen", "Herophilus", "Aristotle"],
        "correct_answer": "Herophilus"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the god of wine, fertility, and theater?",
        "options": ["Apollo", "Dionysus", "Hermes", "Hephaestus"],
        "correct_answer": "Dionysus"
      },
      {
        "question": "What was the name of the famous temple dedicated to Athena on the Acropolis of Athens?",
        "options": ["Parthenon", "Pantheon", "Acropolis", "Temple of Zeus"],
        "correct_answer": "Parthenon"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the goddess of the hearth, home, and family?",
        "options": ["Hestia", "Demeter", "Athena", "Aphrodite"],
        "correct_answer": "Hestia"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which Greek historian chronicled the history of the Peloponnesian War?",
        "options": ["Herodotus", "Thucydides", "Xenophon", "Polybius"],
        "correct_answer": "Thucydides"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the famous Greek philosopher known as the 'Father of Western Philosophy'?",
        "options": ["Socrates", "Aristotle", "Pythagoras", "Plato"],
        "correct_answer": "Socrates"
      },
      {
        "question": "What was the name of the famous Greek poet known for his epic poems 'The Iliad' and 'The Odyssey'?",
        "options": ["Homer", "Hesiod", "Aesop", "Pindar"],
        "correct_answer": "Homer"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which Greek city-state was known for its powerful navy?",
        "options": ["Athens", "Sparta", "Corinth", "Thebes"],
        "correct_answer": "Athens"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the famous Greek playwright known for his comedies such as 'Lysistrata' and 'The Clouds'?",
        "options": ["Sophocles", "Euripides", "Aeschylus", "Aristophanes"],
        "correct_answer": "Aristophanes"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    'level': 21,
    "questions": [
      {
        "question": "Who was the famous Greek philosopher known for his work on ethics and virtue?",
        "options": ["Socrates", "Aristotle", "Plato", "Pythagoras"],
        "correct_answer": "Aristotle"
      },
      {
        "question": "What was the name of the famous temple dedicated to Hera in Olympia?",
        "options": ["Parthenon", "Temple of Artemis", "Acropolis", "Temple of Hera"],
        "correct_answer": "Temple of Hera"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the goddess of love, beauty, and desire?",
        "options": ["Hestia", "Athena", "Hera", "Aphrodite"],
        "correct_answer": "Aphrodite"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which Greek hero was known for his slaying of the Gorgon Medusa?",
        "options": ["Heracles", "Perseus", "Achilles", "Theseus"],
        "correct_answer": "Perseus"
      },
      {
        "question": "What was the name of the famous school of philosophy founded by Aristotle?",
        "options": ["Epicureanism", "Stoicism", "Cynicism", "Lyceum"],
        "correct_answer": "Lyceum"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the famous Greek playwright known for his tragedies such as 'Oedipus Rex'?",
        "options": ["Sophocles", "Euripides", "Aeschylus", "Aristophanes"],
        "correct_answer": "Sophocles"
      },
      {
        "question": "What was the name of the famous battle in which the Greeks defeated the Persians?",
        "options": ["Battle of Thermopylae", "Battle of Marathon", "Battle of Salamis", "Battle of Plataea"],
        "correct_answer": "Battle of Marathon"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the god of the underworld and the ruler of the dead?",
        "options": ["Zeus", "Hades", "Poseidon", "Apollo"],
        "correct_answer": "Hades"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which Greek mathematician calculated the value of pi and invented the screw pump?",
        "options": ["Euclid", "Archimedes", "Pythagoras", "Eudoxus"],
        "correct_answer": "Archimedes"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the goddess of agriculture, fertility, and the harvest?",
        "options": ["Aphrodite", "Hera", "Artemis", "Demeter"],
        "correct_answer": "Demeter"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    'level': 22,
    "questions": [
      {
        "question": "Who was the famous Greek philosopher known for his concept of atomism?",
        "options": ["Socrates", "Aristotle", "Pythagoras", "Democritus"],
        "correct_answer": "Democritus"
      },
      {
        "question": "What was the name of the famous temple dedicated to Zeus in Olympia?",
        "options": ["Parthenon", "Temple of Artemis", "Acropolis", "Temple of Zeus"],
        "correct_answer": "Temple of Zeus"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the goddess of the hearth, home, and family?",
        "options": ["Hestia", "Demeter", "Athena", "Aphrodite"],
        "correct_answer": "Hestia"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which Greek hero was known for his journey to the underworld to rescue his wife, Eurydice?",
        "options": ["Orpheus", "Perseus", "Heracles", "Jason"],
        "correct_answer": "Orpheus"
      },
      {
        "question": "What was the name of the famous school of philosophy founded by Epicurus?",
        "options": ["Epicureanism", "Stoicism", "Cynicism", "Academy"],
        "correct_answer": "Epicureanism"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the famous Greek sculptor known for his statue of 'Aphrodite of Knidos'?",
        "options": ["Phidias", "Praxiteles", "Polykleitos", "Lysippos"],
        "correct_answer": "Praxiteles"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which Greek goddess was known as the virgin huntress?",
        "options": ["Athena", "Hera", "Artemis", "Demeter"],
        "correct_answer": "Artemis"
      },
      {
        "question": "What was the name of the famous battle in which the Greeks decisively defeated the Persians?",
        "options": ["Battle of Thermopylae", "Battle of Marathon", "Battle of Salamis", "Battle of Plataea"],
        "correct_answer": "Battle of Plataea"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the Greek god of wine, fertility, and theater?",
        "options": ["Apollo", "Dionysus", "Hermes", "Hephaestus"],
        "correct_answer": "Dionysus"
      },
      {
        "question": "What was the name of the famous Greek mathematician known for his work on number theory and geometry?",
        "options": ["Euclid", "Archimedes", "Eudoxus", "Pythagoras"],
        "correct_answer": "Pythagoras"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    'level': 23,
    "questions": [
      {
        "question": "Who was the famous Greek historian known as the 'Father of History'?",
        "options": ["Herodotus", "Thucydides", "Xenophon", "Polybius"],
        "correct_answer": "Herodotus"
      },
      {
        "question": "What was the name of the famous temple dedicated to Zeus in Olympia?",
        "options": ["Parthenon", "Temple of Artemis", "Acropolis", "Temple of Zeus"],
        "correct_answer": "Temple of Zeus"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the goddess of the hearth, home, and family?",
        "options": ["Hestia", "Demeter", "Athena", "Aphrodite"],
        "correct_answer": "Hestia"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which Greek hero was known for his journey to the underworld to rescue his wife, Eurydice?",
        "options": ["Orpheus", "Perseus", "Heracles", "Jason"],
        "correct_answer": "Orpheus"
      },
      {
        "question": "What was the name of the famous school of philosophy founded by Epicurus?",
        "options": ["Epicureanism", "Stoicism", "Cynicism", "Academy"],
        "correct_answer": "Epicureanism"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the famous Greek sculptor known for his statue of 'Aphrodite of Knidos'?",
        "options": ["Phidias", "Praxiteles", "Polykleitos", "Lysippos"],
        "correct_answer": "Praxiteles"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which Greek goddess was known as the virgin huntress?",
        "options": ["Athena", "Hera", "Artemis", "Demeter"],
        "correct_answer": "Artemis"
      },
      {
        "question": "What was the name of the famous battle in which the Greeks decisively defeated the Persians?",
        "options": ["Battle of Thermopylae", "Battle of Marathon", "Battle of Salamis", "Battle of Plataea"],
        "correct_answer": "Battle of Plataea"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the Greek god of wine, fertility, and theater?",
        "options": ["Apollo", "Dionysus", "Hermes", "Hephaestus"],
        "correct_answer": "Dionysus"
      },
      {
        "question": "What was the name of the famous Greek mathematician known for his work on number theory and geometry?",
        "options": ["Euclid", "Archimedes", "Eudoxus", "Pythagoras"],
        "correct_answer": "Pythagoras"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    'level': 24,
    "questions": [
      {
        "question": "Who was the famous Greek philosopher known for his work on ethics and virtue?",
        "options": ["Socrates", "Aristotle", "Plato", "Pythagoras"],
        "correct_answer": "Aristotle"
      },
      {
        "question": "What was the name of the famous temple dedicated to Hera in Olympia?",
        "options": ["Parthenon", "Temple of Artemis", "Acropolis", "Temple of Hera"],
        "correct_answer": "Temple of Hera"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the goddess of love, beauty, and desire?",
        "options": ["Hestia", "Athena", "Hera", "Aphrodite"],
        "correct_answer": "Aphrodite"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which Greek hero was known for his slaying of the Gorgon Medusa?",
        "options": ["Heracles", "Perseus", "Achilles", "Theseus"],
        "correct_answer": "Perseus"
      },
      {
        "question": "What was the name of the famous school of philosophy founded by Aristotle?",
        "options": ["Epicureanism", "Stoicism", "Cynicism", "Lyceum"],
        "correct_answer": "Lyceum"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the famous Greek playwright known for his tragedies such as 'Oedipus Rex'?",
        "options": ["Sophocles", "Euripides", "Aeschylus", "Aristophanes"],
        "correct_answer": "Sophocles"
      },
      {
        "question": "What was the name of the famous battle in which the Greeks defeated the Persians?",
        "options": ["Battle of Thermopylae", "Battle of Marathon", "Battle of Salamis", "Battle of Plataea"],
        "correct_answer": "Battle of Marathon"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the god of the underworld and the ruler of the dead?",
        "options": ["Zeus", "Hades", "Poseidon", "Apollo"],
        "correct_answer": "Hades"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which Greek mathematician calculated the value of pi and invented the screw pump?",
        "options": ["Euclid", "Archimedes", "Pythagoras", "Eudoxus"],
        "correct_answer": "Archimedes"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the goddess of agriculture, fertility, and the harvest?",
        "options": ["Aphrodite", "Hera", "Artemis", "Demeter"],
        "correct_answer": "Demeter"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    'level': 25,
    "questions": [
      {
        "question": "Who was the Greek philosopher known for his theory of forms and his allegory of the cave?",
        "options": ["Socrates", "Plato", "Aristotle", "Pythagoras"],
        "correct_answer": "Plato"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which Greek city-state was known for its democratic government and naval power?",
        "options": ["Athens", "Sparta", "Corinth", "Thebes"],
        "correct_answer": "Athens"
      },
      {
        "question": "What was the name of the famous temple dedicated to Artemis in Ephesus?",
        "options": ["Parthenon", "Temple of Artemis", "Acropolis", "Temple of Hera"],
        "correct_answer": "Temple of Artemis"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the goddess of the moon, hunting, and childbirth?",
        "options": ["Hestia", "Athena", "Artemis", "Aphrodite"],
        "correct_answer": "Artemis"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which Greek hero undertook the Twelve Labors as punishment for killing his family?",
        "options": ["Heracles", "Perseus", "Achilles", "Theseus"],
        "correct_answer": "Heracles"
      },
      {
        "question": "What was the name of the famous school of philosophy founded by Zeno of Citium?",
        "options": ["Epicureanism", "Stoicism", "Cynicism", "Academy"],
        "correct_answer": "Stoicism"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the famous Greek playwright known for his satirical comedies?",
        "options": ["Sophocles", "Euripides", "Aeschylus", "Aristophanes"],
        "correct_answer": "Aristophanes"
      },
      {
        "question": "What was the name of the famous battle in which the Greeks defeated the Persian fleet?",
        "options": ["Battle of Thermopylae", "Battle of Marathon", "Battle of Salamis", "Battle of Plataea"],
        "correct_answer": "Battle of Salamis"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the Greek god of wine, fertility, and theater?",
        "options": ["Apollo", "Dionysus", "Hermes", "Hephaestus"],
        "correct_answer": "Dionysus"
      },
      {
        "question": "What was the name of the famous Greek mathematician known for his work on number theory and geometry?",
        "options": ["Euclid", "Archimedes", "Eudoxus", "Pythagoras"],
        "correct_answer": "Pythagoras"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    'level': 26,
    "questions": [
      {
        "question": "Who was the famous Greek philosopher known for his work on ethics and virtue?",
        "options": ["Socrates", "Aristotle", "Plato", "Pythagoras"],
        "correct_answer": "Aristotle"
      },
      {
        "question": "What was the name of the famous temple dedicated to Hera in Olympia?",
        "options": ["Parthenon", "Temple of Artemis", "Acropolis", "Temple of Hera"],
        "correct_answer": "Temple of Hera"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the goddess of love, beauty, and desire?",
        "options": ["Hestia", "Athena", "Hera", "Aphrodite"],
        "correct_answer": "Aphrodite"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which Greek hero was known for his slaying of the Gorgon Medusa?",
        "options": ["Heracles", "Perseus", "Achilles", "Theseus"],
        "correct_answer": "Perseus"
      },
      {
        "question": "What was the name of the famous school of philosophy founded by Aristotle?",
        "options": ["Epicureanism", "Stoicism", "Cynicism", "Lyceum"],
        "correct_answer": "Lyceum"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the famous Greek playwright known for his tragedies such as 'Oedipus Rex'?",
        "options": ["Sophocles", "Euripides", "Aeschylus", "Aristophanes"],
        "correct_answer": "Sophocles"
      },
      {
        "question": "What was the name of the famous battle in which the Greeks defeated the Persians?",
        "options": ["Battle of Thermopylae", "Battle of Marathon", "Battle of Salamis", "Battle of Plataea"],
        "correct_answer": "Battle of Marathon"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the god of the underworld and the ruler of the dead?",
        "options": ["Zeus", "Hades", "Poseidon", "Apollo"],
        "correct_answer": "Hades"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which Greek mathematician calculated the value of pi and invented the screw pump?",
        "options": ["Euclid", "Archimedes", "Pythagoras", "Eudoxus"],
        "correct_answer": "Archimedes"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the goddess of agriculture, fertility, and the harvest?",
        "options": ["Aphrodite", "Hera", "Artemis", "Demeter"],
        "correct_answer": "Demeter"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    'level': 27,
    "questions": [
      {
        "question": "Who was the famous Greek philosopher known for his theory of forms and his allegory of the cave?",
        "options": ["Socrates", "Plato", "Aristotle", "Pythagoras"],
        "correct_answer": "Plato"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which Greek city-state was known for its democratic government and naval power?",
        "options": ["Athens", "Sparta", "Corinth", "Thebes"],
        "correct_answer": "Athens"
      },
      {
        "question": "What was the name of the famous temple dedicated to Artemis in Ephesus?",
        "options": ["Parthenon", "Temple of Artemis", "Acropolis", "Temple of Hera"],
        "correct_answer": "Temple of Artemis"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the goddess of the moon, hunting, and childbirth?",
        "options": ["Hestia", "Athena", "Artemis", "Aphrodite"],
        "correct_answer": "Artemis"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which Greek hero undertook the Twelve Labors as punishment for killing his family?",
        "options": ["Heracles", "Perseus", "Achilles", "Theseus"],
        "correct_answer": "Heracles"
      },
      {
        "question": "What was the name of the famous school of philosophy founded by Zeno of Citium?",
        "options": ["Epicureanism", "Stoicism", "Cynicism", "Academy"],
        "correct_answer": "Stoicism"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the famous Greek playwright known for his satirical comedies?",
        "options": ["Sophocles", "Euripides", "Aeschylus", "Aristophanes"],
        "correct_answer": "Aristophanes"
      },
      {
        "question": "What was the name of the famous battle in which the Greeks defeated the Persian fleet?",
        "options": ["Battle of Thermopylae", "Battle of Marathon", "Battle of Salamis", "Battle of Plataea"],
        "correct_answer": "Battle of Salamis"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the Greek god of wine, fertility, and theater?",
        "options": ["Apollo", "Dionysus", "Hermes", "Hephaestus"],
        "correct_answer": "Dionysus"
      },
      {
        "question": "What was the name of the famous Greek mathematician known for his work on number theory and geometry?",
        "options": ["Euclid", "Archimedes", "Eudoxus", "Pythagoras"],
        "correct_answer": "Pythagoras"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    'level': 28,
    "questions": [
      {
        "question": "Who was the famous Greek philosopher known for his work on ethics and virtue?",
        "options": ["Socrates", "Aristotle", "Plato", "Pythagoras"],
        "correct_answer": "Aristotle"
      },
      {
        "question": "What was the name of the famous temple dedicated to Hera in Olympia?",
        "options": ["Parthenon", "Temple of Artemis", "Acropolis", "Temple of Hera"],
        "correct_answer": "Temple of Hera"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the goddess of love, beauty, and desire?",
        "options": ["Hestia", "Athena", "Hera", "Aphrodite"],
        "correct_answer": "Aphrodite"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which Greek hero was known for his slaying of the Gorgon Medusa?",
        "options": ["Heracles", "Perseus", "Achilles", "Theseus"],
        "correct_answer": "Perseus"
      },
      {
        "question": "What was the name of the famous school of philosophy founded by Aristotle?",
        "options": ["Epicureanism", "Stoicism", "Cynicism", "Lyceum"],
        "correct_answer": "Lyceum"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the famous Greek playwright known for his tragedies such as 'Oedipus Rex'?",
        "options": ["Sophocles", "Euripides", "Aeschylus", "Aristophanes"],
        "correct_answer": "Sophocles"
      },
      {
        "question": "What was the name of the famous battle in which the Greeks defeated the Persians?",
        "options": ["Battle of Thermopylae", "Battle of Marathon", "Battle of Salamis", "Battle of Plataea"],
        "correct_answer": "Battle of Marathon"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the god of the underworld and the ruler of the dead?",
        "options": ["Zeus", "Hades", "Poseidon", "Apollo"],
        "correct_answer": "Hades"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which Greek mathematician calculated the value of pi and invented the screw pump?",
        "options": ["Euclid", "Archimedes", "Pythagoras", "Eudoxus"],
        "correct_answer": "Archimedes"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the goddess of agriculture, fertility, and the harvest?",
        "options": ["Aphrodite", "Hera", "Artemis", "Demeter"],
        "correct_answer": "Demeter"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    'level': 29,
    "questions": [
      {
        "question": "Who was the Greek philosopher known for his theory of forms and his allegory of the cave?",
        "options": ["Socrates", "Plato", "Aristotle", "Pythagoras"],
        "correct_answer": "Plato"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which Greek city-state was known for its democratic government and naval power?",
        "options": ["Athens", "Sparta", "Corinth", "Thebes"],
        "correct_answer": "Athens"
      },
      {
        "question": "What was the name of the famous temple dedicated to Artemis in Ephesus?",
        "options": ["Parthenon", "Temple of Artemis", "Acropolis", "Temple of Hera"],
        "correct_answer": "Temple of Artemis"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the goddess of the moon, hunting, and childbirth?",
        "options": ["Hestia", "Athena", "Artemis", "Aphrodite"],
        "correct_answer": "Artemis"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which Greek hero undertook the Twelve Labors as punishment for killing his family?",
        "options": ["Heracles", "Perseus", "Achilles", "Theseus"],
        "correct_answer": "Heracles"
      },
      {
        "question": "What was the name of the famous school of philosophy founded by Zeno of Citium?",
        "options": ["Epicureanism", "Stoicism", "Cynicism", "Academy"],
        "correct_answer": "Stoicism"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the famous Greek playwright known for his satirical comedies?",
        "options": ["Sophocles", "Euripides", "Aeschylus", "Aristophanes"],
        "correct_answer": "Aristophanes"
      },
      {
        "question": "What was the name of the famous battle in which the Greeks defeated the Persian fleet?",
        "options": ["Battle of Thermopylae", "Battle of Marathon", "Battle of Salamis", "Battle of Plataea"],
        "correct_answer": "Battle of Salamis"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the Greek god of wine, fertility, and theater?",
        "options": ["Apollo", "Dionysus", "Hermes", "Hephaestus"],
        "correct_answer": "Dionysus"
      },
      {
        "question": "What was the name of the famous Greek mathematician known for his work on number theory and geometry?",
        "options": ["Euclid", "Archimedes", "Eudoxus", "Pythagoras"],
        "correct_answer": "Pythagoras"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    'level': 30,
    "questions": [
      {
        "question": "Who was the Greek philosopher known for his work on ethics and virtue?",
        "options": ["Socrates", "Aristotle", "Plato", "Pythagoras"],
        "correct_answer": "Aristotle"
      },
      {
        "question": "What was the name of the famous temple dedicated to Hera in Olympia?",
        "options": ["Parthenon", "Temple of Artemis", "Acropolis", "Temple of Hera"],
        "correct_answer": "Temple of Hera"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the goddess of love, beauty, and desire?",
        "options": ["Hestia", "Athena", "Hera", "Aphrodite"],
        "correct_answer": "Aphrodite"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which Greek hero was known for his slaying of the Gorgon Medusa?",
        "options": ["Heracles", "Perseus", "Achilles", "Theseus"],
        "correct_answer": "Perseus"
      },
      {
        "question": "What was the name of the famous school of philosophy founded by Aristotle?",
        "options": ["Epicureanism", "Stoicism", "Cynicism", "Lyceum"],
        "correct_answer": "Lyceum"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the famous Greek playwright known for his tragedies such as 'Oedipus Rex'?",
        "options": ["Sophocles", "Euripides", "Aeschylus", "Aristophanes"],
        "correct_answer": "Sophocles"
      },
      {
        "question": "What was the name of the famous battle in which the Greeks defeated the Persians?",
        "options": ["Battle of Thermopylae", "Battle of Marathon", "Battle of Salamis", "Battle of Plataea"],
        "correct_answer": "Battle of Marathon"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the god of the underworld and the ruler of the dead?",
        "options": ["Zeus", "Hades", "Poseidon", "Apollo"],
        "correct_answer": "Hades"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which Greek mathematician calculated the value of pi and invented the screw pump?",
        "options": ["Euclid", "Archimedes", "Pythagoras", "Eudoxus"],
        "correct_answer": "Archimedes"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who was the goddess of agriculture, fertility, and the harvest?",
        "options": ["Aphrodite", "Hera", "Artemis", "Demeter"],
        "correct_answer": "Demeter"
      }
    ]
  },
];
